module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who was the 21st president of the United States?', 
    a: 'Rutherford B. Hayes',
    b: 'William Jennings Bryan',
    c: 'Chester A. Arthur',
    d: 'Warren G. Harding',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What toy company manufactures the hoverboard featured in Back to the Future part 2', 
    a: 'Hasbro',
    b: 'Mattel',
    c: 'Nerf',
    d: 'Fisher-Price',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What element has the highest melting point', 
    a: 'Cesium',
    b: 'Titanium',
    c: 'Platinum',
    d: 'Tungsten',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the longest running TV show in US history?', 
    a: 'The Simpsons',
    b: 'Gunsmoke',
    c: 'Guiding Light',
    d: 'Saturday Night Live',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Yul Brynner starred in an adaptation of this famous Akira Kurosawa film', 
    a: 'Hidden Fortress',
    b: 'Throne of Blood',
    c: 'Rashomon',
    d: 'Seven Samurai',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'If you needed a new hat you would go see a ________', 
    a: 'Milner',
    b: 'Fromager',
    c: 'Haberdasher',
    d: 'Cobbler',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Bruce Willis film is an adaption of Akira Kurosawa\'s Yojimbo', 
    a: 'Die Hard',
    b: 'The Jackal',
    c: 'Last Man Standing',
    d: 'The Last Boy Scout',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the movie Spinal Tap, what member is constantly dying? ', 
    a: 'Guitaris',
    b: 'Vocalist',
    c: 'Bassist',
    d: 'Drummer',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a noble gas', 
    a: 'Hadron',
    b: 'Neon',
    c: 'Krypton',
    d: 'Xenon',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the e=mc2 equation, C stands for "Constant", which is what?',
    a: 'Earth\'s gravity',
    b: 'The speed of light',
    c: 'rate of universal expansion',
    d: 'mass of the sun',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];